let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Address of a website is known as _______",
        answer: "Uniform Resource Locator",
        options: [
            "Universe Resource Locator",
            "Uniform Resource Location",
            "Uniform Resource Locator",
            "Universe Resource Location"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the full form of OCR?",
        answer: "Optical Character Recognition",
        options: [
            "Optical Character Recognition",
            "Optical Central Reader",
            "Optimized Character Reader",
            "Optical Character Response"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the use of <strong> in HTML?",
        answer: "Makes the text as important",
        options: [
            "Displays as added text",
            "Makes the text as important",
            "Highlights the text",
            "Displays as strike out text"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Machine Learning is the subset of?",
        answer: "Artificial Intelligence",
        options: [
            "Deep Learning",
            "Data Learing",
            "Artificial Intelligence",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which is vaild C expression?",
        answer: "int my_num = 100000",
        options: [
            "int my_num = 100,000",
            "int my_num = 100000",
            "int my num = 100000",
            "int $my_num = 100000"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which is the equality operator?",
        answer: "==",
        options: [
            ">=",
            "<=",
            "!=",
            "=="
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What does CSS stands for?",
        answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
        options: [
            "Common Style Sheet",
            "Colorful Style Sheet",
            "Computer Style Sheet",
            "Cascading Style Sheet"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What does PHP stands for?",
        answer: "Hypertext Preprocessor",
        options: [
            "Hypertext Preprocessor",
            "Hypertext Programming",
            "Hypertext Preprogramming",
            "Hometext Preprocessor"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What does SQL stands for?",
        answer: "Structured Query Language",
        options: [
            "Stylish Question Language",
            "Stylesheet Query Language",
            "Statement Question Language",
            "Structured Query Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What does XML stands for?",
        answer: "EXtensible Markup Language",
        options: [
            "EXtra Modern Link",
            "EXtensible Markup Language",
            "Example Markup Language",
            "X-Markup Language"
        ]
    },
]